Guide to the Yale Repertory Theatre Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records of the Yale Repertory Theatre, circa 1941-2001; Accession 2003-A-022
  - 1999 -2000 Season
    - Richard III, 3/16 -4/8/2000 (Box 1)
    - Geography II: Tree, 4/20 -5/13/2000 (Box 1)
  - 2000 -2001 Season
    - Mump and Smoot In Something Else With Zug, 9/14 -10/7/2000 (Box 1)
    - Rice Boy, 10/19 -11/11/2000 (Box 1)
    - Heaven, 11/24 -12/16/2000 (Box 1)
    - The Way of the World, 2/9 -3/3/2001 (Box 1)
    - The Birds, 3/22 -4/14/2001 (Box 1)
    - Big Night, 4/26 -5/19/2001 (Box 1)
  - 1998 -1999 Season
    - Peter and Wendy, 9/17 -10/3/1998 (Box 2)
    - Galileo, 10/22 -11/14/1998 (Box 2)
    - Crumbs from the Table of Joy, 11/27 -12/19/1998 (Box 2)
    - Measure for Measure, 1/28 -2/20/1999 (Box 2)
    - The Glass Menagerie, 3/18 -4/10/1999 (Box 2)
    - Hay Fever, 4/29 -5/22/1999 (Box 2)
  - 1994 -1995 Season
    - Antigone in New York, 10/20 -11/12/1994 (Box 3)
    - The Marriage of Figaro/Figaro Gets a Divorce, 12/1 -12/17/1994 (Box 3)
    - Twelfth Night, 1/26 -2/18/1995 (Box 3)
    - Slavs, 2/24 -3/18/1995 (Box 3)
    - Uncle Vanya, 3/30 -4/15/1995 (Box 3)
    - Le Bourgeous Avant-Garde, 4/27 -5/20/1995 (Box 3)
  - 1995 -1996 Season
    - Le Cirque Invisible, 10/19 -11/4/1995 (Box 3)
    - Pentecost, 11/9 -12/2/1995 (Box 3)
    - Mrs. Warren's Profession, 1/11 -2/3/1996 (Box 3)
    - The Beaux Stratagem, 2/15 -3/9/1996 (Box 3)
    - Venus, 3/14 -3/30/1996 (Box 3)
    - Landscape of the Body, 5/2 -5/25/1996 (Box 3)
  - 1992 -1993 Season
    - The Colored Museum, 11/27 -12/19/1992 (Box 4)
    - Children of Paradise, 1/8 -1/30/1993 (Box 4)
    - St. Joan of the Stockyards, 2/18 -3/13/1993 (Box 4)
    - Escape from Happiness, 3/25 -4/17/1993 (Box 4)
    - The Baltimore Waltz, 4/29 -5/22/1993 (Box 4)
  - 1993 -1994 Season
    - Oleanna, 10/14 -11/6/1993 (Box 4)
    - The Green Bird, 11/27 -12/18/1993 (Box 4)
    - The America Play, 1/13 -2/5/1994 (Box 4)
    - As You Like It, 2/17 -3/12/1994 (Box 4)
    - Mump and Smoot, 3/18 -4/9/1994 (Box 4)
    - The School for Wives, 4/28 -5/21/1994 (Box 4)
  - 1991 -1992 Season
    - On the Verge or the Geography of Learning, 10/10 -11/2/1991 (Box 5)
    - My Children! My Africa!, 11/14 -12/14/1991 (Box 5)
    - Edward the Second, 3/19 -4/11/1992 (Box 5)
    - The Beauty Part, 4/30 -5/23/1992 (Box 5)
    - Hamlet, 10/15 -31/1991 (Box 5)
  - Yale School of Drama and New Dramatists form Partnership, 1/15/1999 (Box 6)
  - Yale Repertory Theatre Fills New Community Outreach Post (Box 6)
  - WYBC and Anti-Crime Youth Council ‘Beat the Odds', 2/2/1998 (Box 6)
  - Yale Rep announces New Haven Auditions for Young Actors, 9/11/1998 (Box 6)
  - Byron Jennings to Play Galileo at Yale Rep, 10/22-11/14/1998 (Box 6)
  - Yionoulis Named Chair of Acting Department at YSD, 9/30/1998 (Box 6)
  - Mabou Mines' Peter and Wendy Takes Flight at Yale Rep, 9/17/1998 (Box 6)
  - YSD/Yale Rep Calendar of Events for the 1998-1999 Season, 7/15/1998 (Box 6)
  - Yale Rep announces Directors for 1998-1999 Season, 9/17/1998 (Box 6)
  - Yale Rep announces Season 1998-1999, 9/17/1998 (Box 6)
  - Yale Repertory Theatre announces local auditions in New Haven, 8/26/1998 (Box 6)
  - Yale Rep, Scoozzi make a tasty membership offer, 3/14/1998 (Box 6)
  - Choreographer Lemon, Yale Rep Embark on Second Creation in Geography Trilogy, 2/19/1998 (Box 6)
  - YSD at Yale Rep Showcases Graduating Acting Class in A Midsummer Nights Dream (Box 6)
  - Renowned Playwrights Accept Residences at Yale (Box 6)
  - Arts Leaders Announce New Coalition, Nolan and Ross to Co-Chair (Box 6)
  - The 'Draftiest' Theatre in New Haven? Yale Rep and Redhook Brewery host 'Ale Club', 12/14/1997 (Box 6)
  - Yale Rep offers classic comedy for the Holidays, Wojewodski directs Candida, 11/30/1997 (Box 6)
  - High School Students Receive Master Dance Class, 10/2/1997 (Box 6)
  - ATandT Subsidizes Geography Tickets for New Haven High Schoolers, 10/8/1997 (Box 6)
  - African Artists arrive in New Haven to begin work on Ralph Lemon's Geography, 5/26/1997 (Box 6)
  - Thorton Wilder's 100th Anniversary Committee, 5/9/1997 (Box 6)
  - YSD announces collaboration with the Academy of Dramatic Arts in Saint Petersburg, Russia, 12/12/1996 (Box 6)
  - Thorton Wilder's Centennial Celebration kicks off with February -March events, 2/20/1997 (Box 6)
  - YSD/Yale Rep announces new play reading series, 10/15/1996 (Box 6)
  - Yale Rep announces local auditions in New Haven, 10/16/1996 (Box 6)
  - YSD/Yale Rep names faculty member/production stage manager, 8/2/1996 (Box 6)
  - Plans announced for Thorton Wilder Centennial Celebration, 2/20/1997 (Box 6)
  - Yale Rep announces directors and performance dates for 1996-1997 Season, 5/23/1996 (Box 6)
  - YSD announces 1996 -97 Season, 6/17/1996 (Box 6)
  - Suzan-Lori Parks' Venus Honored with Two Obie Awards, 5/23/1996 (Box 6)
  - YSD Honors Ming Cho Lee with Donald M. Oenslager, Chair of Design, 3/19/1996 (Box 6)
  - Richard Forema to Direct Yale Rep's World Premiere of Suzan-Lori Parks Venus, 3/14/1996 (Box 6)
  - Everett Quinton to Direct the Beaux Strategem at the Yale Rep, 1/25/1996 (Box 6)
  - Professorship Honoring Donald M. Oenslager Established at the YSD (Box 6)
  - Yale Rep announces New Membership Series, 10/25/1995 (Box 6)
  - Yale Rep announces Special Halloween Performances to benefit Dixwell "Q" House, 10/31/1995 (Box 6)
  - Dwight Edgewood Project, 4/26/1995 (Box 6)
  - Yale Rep's Special Events Series Announces Donald Byrd …, 10/14/1995 (Box 6)
  - YSD/Yale Rep names new public relations director, 12/1995 (Box 6)
  - Richard Foreman to direct Yale Rep's World Premiere of Suzan-Lori Parks' Venus co-produced with …, 3/14/1996 (Box 6)
  - Le Cirque Invisible to open Yale Repertory Theatre Season, 10/19/1995 (Box 6)
  - Artistic Director Stand Wojewodski, Jr. Announces YRT 1995-1996 Season, 5/11/1995 (Box 6)
  - Dean Stan Wojewodski, Jr. Announces YSD 1995-1996 Season, 9/13/1995 (Box 6)
  - YRT/YSD announces AIDS benefit performance of Le Bourgeois Avant-Garde, 5/10/1995 (Box 6)
  - YSD receives scholarship gift from the Truman Capote Literary Trust, 11/10/1994 (Box 6)
  - Tip Sheet: New Professorship … Earle Gisler First Recipient, 9/29/1994 (Box 6)
  - Yale Rep announces Directors and performance dates for 1994-1995 Season, 10/27/1994 (Box 6)
  - YSD receives grant Educational Foundation of America, 8/11/1994 (Box 6)
  - Five YSD Graduates receive Fox Fellowships, 8/11/1994 (Box 6)
  - New Professorship honoring Director Lloyd Richards established at the YSD, 9/29/1994 (Box 6)
  - YSD 1994 -95 Season Press Release, 5/17/1994 (Box 6)
  - Artistic Director Stan Wojewodski, Jr. announces Yale Rep 1994 -95 Season, 5/17/1994 (Box 6)
  - Yale Rep holds symposium April 4 for Cripped Trust: Explorations of Seamus Hearney's, 4/4/1998 (Box 6)
  - Stanley Kaufmann to lead post-play discussion at Yale Rep, 1/17/1996 (Box 6)
  - Cast set for YRT production…Le Bourgeois Avant-Garde Press Release and Calendar Listing, 3/31/1995 (Box 6)
  - Antigone in New York special added performance on Nov. 9, 1994 (Box 6)
  - Yale Rep presents Janus Glowaki's Antigone in New York directed by Liz Diamond, 9/21/1994 (Box 6)
  - "Leagues"/Actor Presentation Programs (Box 7)
  - The Prompter 1995/1996 Season, 1997/1998 Season (Box 7)
  - Photographs
    - YSD Class Photo/All School Photo 2000/2001 (Box 7)
    - YSD Class Photo/All School Photo 1999/2000 (Box 7)
    - Class Photos 1998/1999 (Box 7)
    - 1997/1998 YSD Class Photo/Headshots/All School Photo (Box 7)
    - 1996/1997 YSD Class Photo/Headshots/All School Photo (Box 7)
    - 1995/1996 Class Photos and head shots (Box 7)
    - 1994/1995 Class Photos (Box 7)
    - 1993/1994 Photos (Box 7)
    - 1992/1993 Photos (Box 7)
    - Class Photos
      - 1991/1992 (Box 7)
      - 1990/1991 (Box 7)
      - 1989/1990 (Box 7)
      - 1988/1989 (Box 7)
      - 1987/1988 (Box 7)
      - 1986/1987 (Box 7)
      - 1985/1986 (Box 8)
      - 1984/1985 (Box 8)
    - Commencement Photos 1984 -87 (Box 8)
  - The Alchemist, 12/7 -10/72 (Box 9)
  - Amnestia, 3/31 -4/4/2002 (Box 9)
  - The Art of Success 10/24 -28/1995 (Box 9)
  - As I Lay Dying, 3/27 -4/2/1982 (Box 9)
  - As You Like It, 5/2 -6/1989 (Box 9)
  - At War with the Army, 2/18 -21/1948 (Box 9)
  - Baal, 10/21 -24/1981 (Box 9)
  - Bakkhai, 10/29 -11/2/1981 (Box 9)
  - Bartholomew Fair, 1974 -75 (Box 9)
  - The Bathhouse, 4/3 -6/1985 (Box 9)
  - Benten Kozo (Box 9)
  - The Bewitched, 10/27 -30/1982 (Box 9)
  - Big Divinity, 5/7 -10/1986 (Box 9)
  - Birthday Party 1982 -83 (Box 9)
  - The Blind, 3/10 -14/1998 (Box 9)
  - Blood Wedding 10/26 -29/1983 (Box 9)
  - Caucasian Chalk Circle, 11/30 -12/6/2000 (Box 9)
  - Caucasian Chalk Circle, 12/11 -14/1985 (Box 9)
  - The Cherry Orchard, 12/14 -18/1993 (Box 9)
  - The Cherry Orchard, 1941 (Box 9)
  - Colorado Catechism, 1989 -90 (Box 9)
  - The Crazy Locomotive, 12/9 -15/1999 (Box 9)
  - The Devil's Disciple, 1/22 -26/1964 (Box 9)
  - Dido and Aeneas, 1952 -53 (Box 9)
  - Dr. Faustus Lights the Lights, 12/8 -12/1987 (Box 9)
  - Don Juan, 1/26 -30/1993 (Box 9)
  - Dottie's House, 1976 -77 (Box 9)
  - The Dragon, 4/1 -4/1987 (Box 9)
  - Drums in the Night, 1979 -80 (Box 9)
  - The Duchess of Malfi, 3/9 -12/1993 (Box 9)
  - Earth Spirit, 4/29 -31/1976 (Box 9)
  - Edward II, 11/13 -17/75 (Box 9)
  - Electra, 10/29 -11/1/1986 (Box 9)
  - Fanshen, 3/30 -4/2/1983 (Box 9)
  - Foreplay, Doorplay, 1969 (Box 9)
  - Fuente Ovejuna, 4/27 -5/1/1993 (Box 9)
  - Galileo, 5/10 -14/1988 (Box 9)
  - Gilgamesh (Box 9)
  - Golem, 3/8 -13/1999 (Box 9)
  - The Good Person of Szechwan, 12/2 -10/1994 (Box 9)
  - YSD at Yale Rep Showcases Graduating Acting Class in Measure for Measure, 1/28/1999 (Box 10)
  - Reggie Montgomery Directs Yale Rep's Season Finals, Thunder Knocking on the Door, 5/1/1997 (Box 10)
  - YSD at Yale Rep Celebrates Thorton Wilder Centennial with The Skin of Our Teeth, 12/20/1996 (Box 10)
  - Mrs. Warren's Profession directed by Liz Diamond, 1/11 (Box 10)
  - Yale Rep Announces Charles Ludlam's Le Bourgeois Avant-Garde directed by Liz Diamond, 1/31/1995 (Box 10)
  - YSD and New Dramatists present works by Yale playwrights at Mar. 3 Playreading Festival, 3/16/2000 (Box 10)
  - YSD/Yale Rep appoints new marketing director, 6/17/1999 (Box 10)
  - Season 2000 tickets go on sale Yale Rep box office opens to public, 8/2/1999 (Box 10)
  - Two New Haven Theaters receive national grants (Box 10)
  - YSD presents fifth annual Dwight/Edgewood Project, 6/28/1999 (Box 10)
  - Yale Rep announces local auditions in New Haven, 9/24/1999 (Box 10)
  - Cast is set for Shakespeare's As You Like It, Directed by Stan Wojewodski, Jr. at the Yale Rep, 1/28/1994 (Box 10)
  - Calendar Listing: The America Play Lincoln Exhibit by Wendy Allen, 1/13 (Box 10)
  - Yale Rep joins ArtShare in food drive to benefit the Children's Food Drive, 11/24/1993 (Box 10)
  - Casting set for David Mamet's Oleanna at the Yale, 10/14 -11/6 (Box 10)
  - Theatre de la Jeune Lune returns to the Yale Rep to stage Carlo Gozzi's The Green Bird, 11/27 (Box 10)
  - Stan Wojewodski, Jr. announces the 1993 -94 Theater Special Events Series, 10/18/1993 (Box 10)
  - Dean Stan Wojewodski, Jr. announces new faculty for the 1993 -94 academic year at the YSD 9/7/1993 (Box 10)
  - Yale Rep 1993 -94 season calendar (Box 10)
  - Artistic Director finalizes Yale Rep 1993 -94 season, 7/11/1993 (Box 10)
  - Connecticut Critics Circle honors Yale Rep with 10 award nominations, 6/15/1993 (Box 10)
  - Artistic Director Stan Wojewodski, Jr. announces Yale Rep 1993 -94 season featuring dynamic mix, 5/27/1993 (Box 10)
  - Victoria Nolan named Managing Director of Yale Rep/YSD, 4/27/1993 (Box 10)
  - Yale Rep/YSD announces 7 Days of Action, A Community Response to AIDS, 5/2/1993 (Box 10)
  - Stan Wojewodski, Jr. directs Paula Vogel's The Baltimore Waltz at Yale Rep, 4/29 -5/22/1993 (Box 10)
  - The 1992 Jujamcyn Theaters Award goes to Yale Rep/YSD, 11/23/1992 (Box 10)
  - Casting set for Yale Rep's production of George C. Wolfe's The Colored Museum, 11/5/1992 (Box 10)
  - Benjamin Mordecai named Associate Dean of YSD, 9/29/1992 (Box 10)
  - Casting set for Shakespeare's Hamlet directed by Stan Wojewodski, Jr., 9/2/1992 (Box 10)
  - Yale Rep 1992 -93 season schedule, 9/1992 (Box 10)
  - Joyce Friedmann named press and publications director of Yale Rep, 7/24/1992 (Box 10)
  - Yale Rep announces 1992 -93 season, 6/19/1992 (Box 10)
  - YSD announces 1991 -92 season, 10/1991 (Box 10)
  - YRT 1991 -92 season schedule, 8/1991 (Box 10)
  - YRT announces 1991 -92, 6/19/1991 (Box 10)
  - YRT wins special Tony Award, 5/6/1991 (Box 10)
  - YRT announces Equity auditions in New Haven, 7/1991 (Box 10)
  - About the Yale Repertory Theatre, 6/2/1991 (Box 10)
  - Carolco Pictures underwrites Moon, 4/14/1991 (Box 10)
  - Yale Rep announces cast for ONeill's A Moon for the Misbegotten, 4/12/1991 (Box 10)
  - YSD internal memo announcing 1991 -92 season, 4/16/1991 (Box 10)
  - 1992 Special Events -YSD letter, 1/3/1992 (Box 10)
  - WF 12 Devo invite, 12/30/1991 (Box 10)
  - WF 12 prese invite, 12/30/1991 (Box 10)
  - YRT Winterfest Calendar, 11/21/1991 (Box 10)
  - Informal gathering with Stan on Thursday, Dec. 5 at 3 p.m., 11/26/1991 (Box 10)
  - Stan Wojewodski, Jr., named new Dean and Artistic Director of YSD/YRT, 1/10/1991 (Box 10)
  - Cast of Bye Bye Birdie in benefit for Equity Fights AIDS, 3/10/1992 (Box 10)
  - Cast announced for Marlowe's Edward the Second classic, 3/9/1992 (Box 10)
  - Anatoly Smelyansky to speak at Yale on Current Russian Society, 2/18/1992 (Box 10)
  - Rush Tickets available for Yale Rep's Winterfest, 1/26/1992 (Box 10)
  - Yale Rep announces Equity auditions in New Haven, 1/28/1992 (Box 10)
  - Mark Bly named Associate Artistic Director of Yale Rep, 4/28/1992 (Box 10)
  - The Good Person of Szechwan, 12/4 -7/1990 (Box 11)
  - The Great Highway, 4/2 -6/1996 (Box 11)
  - Great Men of Science, 11/21 -22 (Box 11)
  - Hamlet, 4/1 -6/1991 (Box 11)
  - Hamletmachine, 10/31 -11/4/1989 (Box 11)
  - Hamlet, 4/3 -7/1990 (Box 11)
  - Happy End, 5/2 -7/1997 (Box 11)
  - Help Wanted, 10/24 -27/1984 (Box 11)
  - Hostage, 1/23 -26/1984 (Box 11)
  - The House of York, 5/11 -14/1983 (Box 11)
  - Imperceptible Mutabilities, 5/9 -13/1995 (Box 11)
  - Jungle of Cities, 1980 (Box 11)
  - Learned Ladies, 1981 (Box 11)
  - L'Aiglon, 5/8 -11/1985 (Box 11)
  - Life Is A Dream, 1980 (Box 11)
  - Life Is A Dream, 4/26 -5/1/1999 (Box 11)
  - The Life of Galileo, 5/10 -14/1988 (Box 11)
  - Long Day's Journey into Night, 10/1981 (Box 11)
  - Lorenzaccio, 2/15 -23/1985 (Box 11)
  - The Love of Three Oranges, 11/2 -6/1993 (Box 11)
  - The Lower Depths, 2/4 -12/1983 (Box 11)
  - Lulu, 1975 -76 (Box 11)
  - Mad Dog Blues, 2/1 -4/73 (Box 11)
  - Major Barbara, 5/2 -6/73 (Box 11)
  - Marriage of Bette and Boo, 3/7 -11/73 (Box 11)
  - Master and the Margarita, 1/15 -20/2001 (Box 11)
  - Preliminary announcement (3 plays) of 1987-1988 season, 5/13/1987 (Box 11)
  - Arthur Pepine honored by NEA and President's Committee, 5/13/1987 (Box 11)
  - Fences wins 4 Tony Awards, nabs theatrical triple crown, 6/8/1987 (Box 11)
  - 1987 -88 season announced, 7/31/1987 (Box 11)
  - Rep Equity auditions, 9/11/1987 (Box 11)
  - Sarcophagus opens 1987 -88 season September 18, 9/11/1987 (Box 11)
  - Melons Cast and Designers announced, 10/5/1987 (Box 11)
  - Bunraku lecture/demonstration set at Yale, 10/7/1987 (Box 11)
  - 1987 -88 Yale School of Drama season announced, 10/14/1987 (Box 11)
  - Additional Wednesday matinee December 2 for The Piano Lesson, 10/22/1987 (Box 11)
  - AIDS benefit set for November 10, 10/22/1987 (Box 11)
  - August Wilson to receive key to city Tuesday, November 17, 10/22/1987 (Box 11)
  - Book signing party with August Wilson December 2 at Atticus, 11/24/1987 (Box 11)
  - The Piano Lesson set for Huntington engagement, Jan. 9 -31, 11/27/1987 (Box 11)
  - Calendar Listing: 1987 -88 Season (Box 11)
  - Calendar Listing: O'Neill Celebration (Box 11)
  - Extra Matinee December 16 for The Piano Lesson, 12/2/1987 (Box 12)
  - Winterfest 8 Calendar Listing (Box 12)
  - Winterfest rehearsal underway; casts and designers announced, 1/3/1988 (Box 12)
  - Winterfest seminars begin January 16 with Playwrights at Play, 1/11/1988 (Box 12)
  - O'Neill Calendar Fact Sheet, 1/14/1988 (Box 12)
  - Fest Weekends for Winterfest 8 announced, 1/17/1988 (Box 12)
  - Panelists set for Winterfest seminar #3 and #4, 1/18/1988 (Box 12)
  - Cast announced for O'Neill Plays, 3/7/1988 (Box 12)
  - Lloyd Richards wins Commonwealth Award, 3/10/1988 (Box 12)
  - Three extra Ah Wilderness matinees scheduled, 3/10/1988 (Box 12)
  - O'Neill lectures, 3/29/1988 (Box 12)
  - New York Outer Critics Circle Nominations, 4/27/1988 (Box 12)
  - Drama League Awards for Yale Rep, 4/28/1988 (Box 12)
  - $1,000,000 Grant for Rep, 5/2/1988 (Box 12)
  - Joe Turner, Walk Tony nominations, 5/9/1988 (Box 12)
  - Joe Turner/Mecca NY Drama Critics Circle Award, 5/17/1988 (Box 12)
  - L. Scott Caldwell -Tony Award, 6/6/1988 (Box 12)
  - 1988 -89 Season announced (Box 12)
  - Lloyd Richards term extended at Yale, 9/1/1988 (Box 12)
  - 1988 -89 Yale School of Drama season announced, 9/24/1988 (Box 12)
  - Warrior Ant children's workshop 88 -89, 10/5/1988 (Box 12)
  - Calendar Listing 1988 -89 (Box 12)
  - Revised Alchemist calendar, 1998 -89, 11/21 -12/17/1988 (Box 12)
  - Winterfest 9 -calendar release, 1/10 -2/4/1989 (Box 12)
  - Winterfest 9 -calendar release revised (Box 12)
  - Nikos memorial release, 2/15/1989 (Box 12)
  - Added Moon matinee release, 2/15/1989 (Box 12)
  - 1989 -90 season calendar release, 8/11/1989 (Box 12)
  - Video cast (Henry Winkler, Al Terzi, Diane Smith) set for "Solid Gold", 9/12/1989 (Box 12)
  - Two variations on Hamlet YSD 1989 -90 season, 10/5/1989 (Box 12)
  - 5 Play sub available for 1989 -90 season, 11/13/1989 (Box 12)
  - YRT celebrates a decade of Winterfests, 11/13/1989 (Box 12)
  - Yale Repertory Theatre announces Equity auditions in New Haven, 11/24/1989 (Box 12)
  - Participating artists set for Winterfest 10 seminar, 1/12/1990 (Box 12)
  - Yale Repertory Theatre announces 2ndday of Equity auditions, 1/12/1990 (Box 12)
  - Winterfest 10 calendar, 1/15 -2/10/1990 (Box 12)
  - Dean search committee appointed for Yale School of Drama, 2/15/1990 (Box 12)
  - Yale Rep receives $82,500 from the Lila Wallace -Reader's Digest Fund for world premiere of Two Trains Running, 2/27/1990 (Box 12)
  - Wilson signs books Saturday, March 31 at Atticus Bookstore, 3/23/1990 (Box 12)
  - Yale Rep production of August Wilson's The Piano Lesson nominated for 5 Helen Hayes Awards in Washington D.C., 3/23/1990 (Box 12)
  - Yale Rep adds April 11 matinee for Two Trains Running, 3/26/1990 (Box 12)
  - Lloyd Richards letter to YSD/YRT community re: 90-1991 season, 4/9/1990 (Box 12)
  - Lloyd Richards to celebrate his final season at Yale Rep with three premieres, 4/11/1990 (Box 12)
  - August Wilson's The Piano Lesson, YRT premiere, wins Pulitzer Prize, 4/12/1990 (Box 12)
  - Piano Lesson nominated for 5 Tony Awards, 5/7/1990 (Box 12)
  - Piano Lesson wins New York Drama Critics Circle Award for Best Play, 5/16/1990 (Box 12)
  - Extra matinee for Pygmalion on May 16, 4/30/1990 (Box 12)
  - Carolco sponsors Pygmalion, 4/30/1990 (Box 12)
  - 1990 -91 season announcement, 7/20/1990 (Box 12)
  - 1990 -91 season calendar listing, 8/1990 (Box 13)
  - Equity auditions in New Haven for 1990 -91 season set for September 16, 8/24/1990 (Box 13)
  - Vaclav Havel's Largo Desolato added to 1990 -91 Yale Rep season schedule, 8/24/1990 (Box 13)
  - Ivanov cast announced, 8/30/1990 (Box 13)
  - Smelyansky to give lectures in conjuncetion with Ivanov, 9/14/1990 (Box 13)
  - Oleg Yefremov to receive key to city of New Haven on September 21, 9/17/1990 (Box 13)
  - TV and Radio Tip Sheet: Yefremov to receive key to city of New Haven, 9/20/1990 (Box 13)
  - Largo Desolato cast announced 10/6/1990 (Box 13)
  - Asante Scott named to YSD/YRT Minority Recruitment post, 10/26/1990 (Box 13)
  - Search and Destroy cast announced, 11/19/1990 (Box 13)
  - Winterfest 11 plays selected, 11/30/1990 (Box 13)
  - Winterfest 11 calendar listing, 12/3/1990 (Box 13)
  - Adrian Hall to direct Joshua Sobol's Underground at YRT, 12/17/1990 (Box 13)
  - Winterfest 11 casts announced, 12/21/1990 (Box 13)
  - Yale Rep announces Rush Tickets for Winterfest 11, 1/7/1991 (Box 13)
  - Two of Time Magazines Best of Theater 1990 premiered at YRT, 1/7/1991 (Box 13)
  - Winterfest 11 press invitation, 1/8/1991 (Box 13)
  - Winterfest 11 seminar to explore cultural diversity, 1/17/1991 (Box 13)
  - Panelist selected for final Winterfest 11 seminar on cultural diversity, 1991 (Box 13)
  - Cast announced for Joshua Sobol's Underground, 2/4/1991 (Box 13)
  - Fact Sheet for LA farewell party for Lloyd Richards, 2/11/1991 (Box 13)
  - Rush tickets available for rest of 1990 -91 season, 2/20/1991 (Box 13)
  - Moon for the Misbegotten to close 1990 -91 YRT season, 2/22/1991 (Box 13)
  - Cast for Scapin, 3/11/1991 (Box 13)
  - Memorial service for Dennis Scott, 3/12/1991 (Box 13)
  - School Shows (Box 14)
  - Measure for Measure, 5/6/1987-5/13/1987 (Box 14)
  - Medea, 11/3/1987-11/7/1987 (Box 14)
  - Midsummer Night's Dream, 5/7/1986-5/10/1986 (Box 14)
  - Midsummer Night's Dream, 1962 (Box 14)
  - Mississippi Nude, 12/5/1989-12/9/1989 (Box 14)
  - Misan Trope, 2000 (Box 14)
  - Black Man Who Made the Angels Wait, 3/30/1997-4/5/1991 (Box 14)
  - The Name of Oedipus, 12/10/1991-12/14/1991 (Box 14)
  - The Overcoat (Box 14)
  - Our Town, 1944 (Box 14)
  - Our Town, 5/4/2001-5/9/2001 (Box 14)
  - Pacific Overtures, 12/7/1984-12/15/1984 (Box 14)
  - The Patriarch, 1926 (Box 14)
  - Peer Gynt, 1/21/1981-1/24/1981 (Box 14)
  - Peer Gynt, 4/26/1994-4/30/1994 (Box 14)
  - Pericles, 12/6/1988-12/10/1988 (Box 14)
  - People Vs. God of Vengeance, 5/8/2000-5/13/2000 (Box 14)
  - Pericles, 5/19/1984-5/12/1984 (Box 14)
  - Physicists, 1970 (Box 14)
  - Pilgrims of the Night (Box 14)
  - Pillars of Society, 1982 (Box 14)
  - Platonov, 2/6/1985-2/10/1985 (Box 14)
  - Poor of New York, 1971 (Box 14)
  - The Pope and the Witch, 1996-1997 (Box 14)
  - Prince of Hamburg, 1999 (Box 14)
  - Request Concert (Box 14)
  - Revenger's Tragedy (Box 14)
  - The Meyerhold Project, 10/4/1997 (Box 14)
  - Richard III, 5/1991 (Box 14)
  - The Ride Across Lake Constance, 1996-1997 (Box 14)
  - Romeo and Juliet, 3/1994 (Box 14)
  - Romeo and Juliet, 5/1990 (Box 14)
  - The Road, 1/13/1998-1/17/1998 (Box 14)
  - Rosmes Holm (Box 14)
  - The Royal Parden, 1978-1979 (Box 14)
  - The Skriker, 2000-2001 (Box 14)
  - STE Carmen of the Main, 3/1989 (Box 14)
  - Spring Awakening, 1981-1982 (Box 14)
  - Stage Door, 1991-1992 (Box 14)
  - Subject o Fits, 1969-1970 (Box 14)
  - The Suicide, 1985 (Box 14)
  - Summerfolk, 1980-1981 (Box 14)
  - The Swain, 1/28/1993-1/30/1993 (Box 14)
  - Tartuffe, 1981 (Box 14)
  - Terra Nova, 1975-1976 (Box 14)
  - The Seagull, 1997-1998 (Box 14)
  - The Seagull, 11/1992 (Box 14)
  - Brochure History (Box 15)
  - Subscription Campaign
    - 1970-1971 (Box 15)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 15)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 15)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 15)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 15)
    - 1976-1977 (Box 15)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 15)
    - 1978-1979 (Box 15)
    - 1979-1980 (Box 15)
    - 1980-1981 (Box 15)
    - 1981-1982 (Box 15)
    - 1982-1983 (Box 15)
    - 1983-1984 Renewal (Box 15)
    - 1983-1984 (Box 15)
    - 1984-1985 (Box 15)
  - Misc. (Box 16)
  - Venus, all things Considered, 1996 (Box 16)
  - Triump of Love,Morning Edition, 1998 (Box 16)
  - Open Air New England, 1990 (Box 16)
  - Pill Hill,Lesser (Box 16)
  - Troilus and Cressida, P.Joffee (Box 16)
  - NPR'S "Horizons", 1990 (Box 16)
  - Yale Rep Group Sessions II (Box 16)
  - Moon Over Miami,NPR, 1989 (Box 16)
  - Yale Focus Groups,I Yale Subscribers (Box 16)